[music]
[bell]
>> Only been a few hours on holidays.
>> [music]
>> Only been days that felt like months.
Don't call for you only got life once.
Life [music] move fast when you know
what you want.
>> Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning. Good morning. Welcome or
welcome back to another vlog. I look
like a glazed donut. As you can tell, I
got my scrubs on. I'm about to head out
to work. I just made me a coffee at
home. We are saving that coin. We are
cooking at home. We are eating at home.
We are making coffee at home. We are
doing everything at home these days. So,
I think we're giving the vibes of 9-5
diary, spend the work week with me, um
living alone diaries. I'm really just
bringing y'all along. It's going to be a
regular degular vlog. Y'all know how the
vlogs get when I go to work, when I go
to the gym, when I come home, when I
clean, when I cook. Y'all know how they
get. So, I always got to give that
disclaimer cuz it be them girls in the
comments. I'm about to head out for the
morning. It is currently 7:08 in the
morning. I start my mornings off
listening to Lil Poppa. Rest in peace,
my heart, for real. But, this is what I
start my mornings off. Like, girl, I was
so tired. I did not want to get up out
of bed this morning. Put on some Lil
Poppa. Got to get ready. Straighten my
hair. Put my jewelry on. Nails ain't
done. Don't worry about it. Made my
coffee. About to head out the door. It
is Wednesday. It is midweek. When we
come home, we're going to go to the gym.
As y'all know, every weekday, Monday
through Friday, unless I feel like
taking a break, then I give myself a
break. It's Wednesday, so I do a midweek
reset. My perm is actually a mess.
So, a midweek reset is really needed.
And yeah, I'll probably cook dinner,
just the regular degular things. So far,
it's been a pretty good week. This week
has actually been going by super fast.
So, I'm so excited cuz I'm really
excited for the weekend. I need the
weekend to come. I'm getting my nails
done. Um probably going to book me a
hair appointment. I'm not too sure yet,
but I'm just so excited for the weekend,
girls. So, I made a coffee. I used my
cookie butter Chobani creamer. I don't
know what it is. I haven't been making
coffee at home in like months. So, now
that I finally started back, I have to
like regain my touch cuz it's not really
hitting no more, unfortunately. But, um
I'm finna head out to work. I'm going to
go clock in and make me some money. And
I hope you do the same, sister. So,
let's go ahead and get up off our ass on
this lovely Wednesday. Go make some
money.
And I'll see y'all after work. All
right, y'all. I just got off work. As
y'all can see, I changed my clothes. We
are about to head to the gym.
Immediately after I clock out from that
9-5, I come home, I change clothes, or
else I'm not going to the gym. It is
currently 5:27 in the afternoon. We are
about to head out. Let me tell y'all why
I'm irritated today. So, I ordered
almost $350 worth of stuff off TikTok
Shop. From accessories to workout sets,
cuz if you know me, you know. All my
workout sets, TikTok Shop. I ordered a
whole bunch of stuff. I'm like so
excited, right? So, one I ordered a Aura
Ring dupe. If you know, you know. I
ordered a dupe off TikTok Shop. It said
my package was delivered. I go check the
proof of delivery picture, cuz I'm at
work when it got delivered. It got
delivered to a house.
If you know anything about me, I live in
an apartment. Do I live near any houses?
No. DON'T KNOW WHERE MY package was
delivered to, but it was delivered to a
house. Cool, gave me a refund, no
problem. I ordered this set in like a
the cutest like pastel green color. It
was out for delivery yesterday. I get
notification that says it was basically
failed to deliver. We couldn't deliver
it to you. The reason, no reason. They
said they couldn't contact me. They have
my number and email on file. Okay, cool.
Let that slide. Then, I ordered this set
again in a coral color. It said um out
for delivery today. Proof of delivery,
delivered. It said it was delivered
today. Pull up my proof of delivery. I
check it. It was delivered to my
apartment complex, but it was delivered
They threw it over somebody's balcony.
Not mine, cuz I'm not on the first
floor. They threw it over somebody's
balcony. Whose balcony? I don't you
know. I don't Is it my apartment
complex? Yes. Whose balcony did they
throw it over? I have no clue. They took
a picture of it and it's in somebody's
balcony. I don't know what is going on
with my packages with TikTok Shop, but
I'm about this close to never ordering
again from TikTok Shop. So, I'm wearing
my regular old workout set cuz I don't
have none of my new ones. Back in the
basics. I was excited to wear something
new this whole week, but none of my
stuff has came. I'm sorry, y'all. My
room here is so dirty. This is today's
outfit, just this little burgundy set
from Coral Cantin on TikTok. Do we see
the gains or no? I'm going to head out
to the gym. I'm going to record in the
gym. I don't know what today is in the
gym, but y'all my apartment is a wreck.
So, we're going to get this under
control too. It's Wednesday. We got to
do a midweek reset. It's just going to
be a bunch of homey things today. So,
get up. Who text? Get up. Let's get
ready to go work this body out.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right, y'all. I just got back home
from the gym. Guess what I came home to.
Just one. Just one. The one that's still
in somebody's apartment balcony in this
neighborhood is still missing. This is
the one they failed to deliver yesterday
and they re-attempted delivery today.
But, the chatbot on TikTok told me they
wasn't going to attempt to deliver again
and they would send it to the back to
the warehouse. But,
we got her. Let's unbox her. This is
from Coral Cantin. This is literally the
same set I have on just in a different
color. So, Coral Cantin be having your
body looking tea. Coral Cantin. I'mma
put it on the screen cuz it probably
sound like I'm saying a whole bunch of
nothing. All of my workout sets are
linked in my TikTok shop. They're all
from TikTok. Anything you see me in
going to the gym is from TikTok.
This green is finna be Oh my god, she's
perfect. I can't wait to wear this. I'm
really going to wear it tomorrow. These
I don't know if y'all can see the little
words at the bottom. Can y'all see?
That's like put on the thing. Soon as
you wash it, all them words is going to
come off. I don't have no words on none
of my Coral K Anns says.
And then the bottoms, this is so cute.
Wish I would have got my Coral one, too.
I mean, it's here. Hopefully the people
is nice enough to give it back, but
we'll see. And then these are the shorts
that on the back they say, you see?
Coral K Anns. Anyways, oh also let me
show y'all from yesterday. Ignore my
apartment, it's a mess. Yes, we're going
to clean up.
Yesterday I got a PR package from
I got a PR package from Naturium. They
just dropped their new SPF 50
moisturizer, and y'all know everything I
have, I love. So, I'm excited to try
this. I got it yesterday. I took some
pictures and I thanked them. Oh, they
did never play about their PR packaging,
like literally ever. As of right now,
this is all the packages we have. Y'all,
I need to hurry up and cook dinner, and
I need to clean this apartment cuz I'm
not trying to be up all night. For
dinner we are making I'm not even going
to record me cooking it cuz it's very
simple, it's very quick. I'm making a
Caesar pasta salad with salmon. I bought
a big slab of salmon, cut it up, cooked
it all. So, now I have like two pieces
left, and that's been helping me get
through the week. So, I'm not even going
to film it. I'll put it together with
y'all, but that's about it. And I'll
come back once it's done. So, let me get
in that cooking mode.
And then we got to clean up cuz this
looks a mess. We are about to put
together my meal. First things first, I
just got pasta noodles. Bare pasta
noodles, right? I'm going to take this
out, pour it in this bowl. Caesar
dressing.
Caesar dressing, as little or as much as
you want. I personally season it, so I
use the salad supreme mix, and then I
just use black pepper. Those are the
only two seasonings that I use on this.
I add a little bit of ranch on top of
the Caesar.
And y'all, they say don't eat lettuce
right now. Just cuz I'm eating it, that
that don't go eat it. I'm just I don't
know, I just don't got time. I threw
some lettuce in here. Now I'm just going
to stir that up as well.
It looks like a whole bunch of nothing.
I'm not going to lie. Mozzarella cheese,
I'm just going to sprinkle it all on
top.
I'm a cheese person, so.
Croutons, literally I'm just throwing
stuff I had in the house together. So
we're making it work. This is one of
those meals. I think y'all be thinking
like, oh she be Oh,
oh she be cooking and stuff all the
time. She always eat good. Sometimes
I just throw stuff together like this.
But I promise you it's never I do not
cook like
somebody mama every day. Then to top it
off, we're going to do some protein and
I am doing salmon. She's done. That's
it. That's all. Eating my dinner,
minding my business.
Thank you.
Thank you. And see this is what I'm
talking about. When you live in a good
community with good folk, they're going
to come They're going to come through
for you. She said I stepped outside of
my balcony and I was like, what the hell
is this? I was like, girl exactly. I
said I was I'm not going to lie.
I was definitely going to jump over your
balcony and go get it myself, but I was
like, you know what? I have faith
they're going to bring it to me and they
did. Her and her husband walked up to my
door and brought me my package. Shout
out to them. Them them them. Y'all I'm
so excited to work out this weekend. I
got two new sets. I got three more on
the way, which they're all delayed. I
don't know what's going on with TikTok
Shop, but I'm about to stop ordering
from them. Like for real, cuz this is
getting out of hand. Ooh, this going to
be bomb on the skin. Super bomb and it's
the halter top. I really like these cuz
if you know I have a bigger chest and
these just
you know. Then the bottom, same thing.
Scrunch booty. I like the scrunch booty.
A lot of people don't, but I like it.
Scrunch butt
shorts. Hopefully those come this week
so I can show y'all. But I got to clean
this kitchen, boo. I'm tired of looking
at it. I just want to lay down, read my
book, drink my liquid chlorophyll, and
go to bed. I don't really want to do too
much during the week. Like I'm chill,
I'm calm, I'm not into all that. So it's
about 9:00. Let me straighten up real
quick, real fast, and we're going to get
ready for bed. One thing about I get
stuff done and I get it done quickly. I
am showered, my apartment is clean.
She's clean. We even got a candle going
in the back. Body oil up.
9:38. But anyways, we got a little sweet
treat today. And let me tell you what
this is. This is a protein muffin.
Right? And I really cannot understand
the gym rats and the protein stuff cuz
they always be trifling. But everybody
in the gym was like, "Oh, what you" cuz
somebody was in there selling them. So I
was like, "Oh, which one you got?" This
is a Biscoff.
A Biscoff protein muffin. She looks
good. She looks amazing, actually. She
Ooh.
She even smells good, I'm not going to
lie. I would cuz actually good. Cuz
y'all tried like a protein brownie thing
the other day. Disgusting. Disgusting.
So I'm really like eeked out with the
whole protein stuff. Like, whatever. But
this is a Biscoff protein like cupcake
muffin.
Okay, I really don't like icing, y'all.
So let me see. All right, it's hard.
We got to warm this up. This good. Wow,
I'm low-key turning this up.
This is so freaking good. I think it has
like 20-something grams of protein in
it. It's filling on the inside. I'm
literally making love
to this, whatever the hell it is. Oh my
god.
All right, y'all.
I'll see y'all back in the room. All
right, y'all. I'm in the bed. We are
about to relax. It is I don't even know
what time it is, girl.
9:53. I'm losing some lashes, so I'm
going to just go ahead and redo my
lashes tomorrow. I'm going to just just
ignore it tonight. Tonight is not that
big of a deal. Don't worry. Don't look
too hard. I came up on here to tell
y'all we are reading a new book. We are.
So y'all, I finished The Housemaid. I
finished it. Literally Saturday night. I
was like, "Girl, I've been sitting on
this too long. Let me finish it." And
when I tell y'all as soon as I picked it
back up is when it got good. Oh my god,
this book was freaking crazy. Like, the
the plot twist on her books. And mind
you, the plot twist is at the very end,
like girl. So, somebody in the comments
told me the second one is better than
the first one, so I'm picking that up
next. I just don't have it in my hands
right now, otherwise that's exactly what
I would have started is the second one.
So, me and my friend are going to have a
movie night cuz we both read it. This is
actually her book. She gave it to me,
and then she said when I finish we're
going to have a movie night, which I'm
excited for, but I had to pick up
another book in the meantime, girl. So,
next read is Want to Know a Secret by
Freida McFadden. I am literally just
like a few pages in. Um, I got this book
from Marshalls for $8.99. Check out your
local Marshalls before you go to Target
and Walmart. So, yeah, this is my new
read. I'm so excited, y'all. I love
being in my reading bag. Like, y'all
please give reading a chance. I used to
be one of them girls I did not want to
pick up a book. Uh, you couldn't you
couldn't pay me to pick up a book, but
now, once I really found what type of
books I like, Freida McFadden.
Freida McFadden, Freida McFadden, Freida
McFadden. That's what type of books I
like. Once I found what type of books I
like and what type of books can really
have me set. Colleen Hoover is good,
TOO. I DON'T get me wrong, I love I
started with Colleen Hoover, she's cool,
but once I got to that Freida McFadden,
that's a different type of You know what
I'm saying? So, yeah, y'all, if you ever
have any book wrecks, let me know. I'm
finna to read my book until I get
sleepy, which usually doesn't take too
long. Um, that's it. So, good night. And
I don't know when tomorrow,
but I'll see y'all tomorrow. Y'all, why
is it days later? I don't know when the
last time I picked the camera up is.
Wait, I don't know the last time when I
picked the camera up is. It is August
1st, Saturday, 9:19 in the morning.
Why am I just now
walking out? Just now walking out. So,
the crazy part about all of this is I
slept with no bonnet last night, no
nothing on my head. They still look
good. But, I'm about to go to a hair
appointment. My hair appointment is at
10:45. It's 9:20. It's now picking up my
wig. So, I'm going to just take this
off, and I'm not going to like take the
braid down. Um, I'm going to just have
her put another wig over it. So, I'm
going to have to shower real quick.
Baby, I'm running off like little to no
sleep. Or, I'm going to take it off and
then just go to my hair appointment with
my braids and have her just slapping up
the wig on. I don't have all day. I
don't want to be there all day.
I don't know. I'm just kind of tired of
this. Like it doesn't even look too bad,
but I'm telling you by Monday morning
it's going to be back here. My wigs be
sliding back and that be THE PROBLEM.
SO,
I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND HOP in the
shower, y'all, and then take this wig
off. And when I see y'all, I need to
drink a coffee or something cuz no. And
then tomorrow we got nails, so
maintenance vlog
part of maintenance? I don't know. Girl,
I don't know. I'm going to hop in the
shower.
See what my hair appointment is.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Y'all, I don't know what it is about
some curly hair on me,
but curly hair has got to be like top
tier. I think it's one of my styles that
really brings like [clears throat]
Kaya out. I don't know. Something about
the curly hair and I did a little bit of
dramatic edges on the side. I think it's
super cute. My girl always eats. And
it's looking like it don't look full
because it's wet. So, once it like poofs
out, it'll be like
you know hair is done. Y'all, I haven't
ate anything all day. It is 2:30.
>> [music]
>> It is 2:30. I have yet to eat anything.
I'm running off of barely any sleep. I
told y'all I got to house sit at 9:00
this morning. Came home, took a shower,
came straight here. And I've been here
since. Like I'm tired. I'm hungry.
I still got stuff to do, girl. So, and I
made plans with my homegirl tonight. So,
never fix my lash though, but we'll
handle that a little bit later. My
camera's about to die anyway, so I'll
probably meet y'all back at the house.
And then tomorrow we get nails. I think
I might double stack my lashes to give
it like a full effect, but I look so
Yeah. Good morning. Good morning. Good
morning. Good Oh, Lord. Hold on. Pause.
It is 1:18 in the afternoon. I'm talking
about good morning. Girl, it's been a
weekend. It's been a weekend. It is
currently Sunday, August 2nd. It is,
like I said, 1:18 in the afternoon. Um I
just went ahead and got myself together.
I kind of straightened my apartment up a
little bit, started laundry. We're about
to get a move on our day. Um this vlog
has been all over the place. I don't
know what this is going to be, but I'm
not going to waste no footage, so it's
still finna go up. I'm sorry my camera
keeps like defocusing. It really pisses
me off when it does this when I'm in the
car. Um I'm about to go to Dunkin'.
We're about to try a new drink. Y'all
haven't had Dunkin' in a while. So, I've
been seeing this like drink everybody's
been trying. It looks really good and
cute and pink and girly. And I have on
pink today, so I'm like
It just gives like let's try a cute pink
drink. Today is nail day. I got my hair
done yesterday. It just is still intact.
I left the house so early. My
appointment is not till 2:30, but I left
the house so early cuz I don't have a
clue in the world on what I'm going to
get. I don't know what I'm about to get,
y'all. Like so, I'm about to just sit in
my car, sit in my car, scroll on
Pinterest, and try to find something.
And then I have to go say ATM cuz
her thing says cash only now. So, yeah,
it's called a vanilla pink cloud latte.
Can y'all see?
Vanilla pink cloud. Let me see what it
is. It's strawberry Ooh, strawberry cold
foam and then it's like a vanilla latte.
That actually sounds really good. It
sounds really good. A vanilla latte with
strawberry cloud or strawberry cold
foam.
We're going to get that. We're literally
about to go to Dunkin. I'm going to get
a small cuz yeah, I've been eating
healthy. I haven't been drinking like
sugary coffee. If I make coffee, I just
do like brown sugar, honey, cinnamon,
like regular sweeteners to sweeten it
up. So, we're going to have a cute girly
Sunday. Um but first, let's go ahead and
get this coffee. I'm so excited to try
it. Okay, y'all, we have the coffee. At
first, he forgot the cold foam. I said,
"Baby, this is the whole point." Um can
y'all see? Y'all know I film in Dlog, so
when I'm showing y'all this, there's no
color. So, I don't know how y'all are
going to see it, but she looks so good.
I'm about to take a picture and we're
about to try it together. Oh my god, I
smell strawberry. I'm so excited.
Let me try to
And you know what?
I see the vision,
but I just think the coffee isn't right
today. The actual latte part, like the
actual coffee part, it tastes kind of
burnt.
But that cold foam is good. Like if this
was made correctly, I'm telling my
coffee just tastes kind of burnt. But I
see the vision. Like I know if I
would've went to a good Dunkin' on a
good day, this would've been fire. So,
now I have a couple minutes into my nail
appointment. I'm about to sit in the
car. Oh my goodness, y'all. Hold on, I'm
about to figure out how to change this.
Okay. Now, I'm about to sit in the car
and scroll down Pinterest and do what
I've been doing, look for some nail
inspo for y'all. I have no idea what I'm
going to get. Like I've been scrolling
Oh, shoot.
I've been scrolling and scrolling and
scrolling trying to find nail inspo, and
I cannot figure out what I want. I
really want Y'all know I'm into
stilettos lately. I love a good stiletto
nail. But I kind of don't want to do
stilettos and I kind of don't want
length. I kind of want to go short. But
at the same time, I really want
stilettos. And at the same time, I kind
of just want to do regular basic French
like I always do. I don't want to do
design, but at the same time, a little
design might be cute. I just don't know
what to do. I really like these, but
like the more I look at them, the more I
don't want them. I was going to get
these in stilettos instead of almond,
but I don't want those anymore. I
thought these were cute, but like when I
look at them too hard, I kind of get
like the ick for some reason with the
polka dots. I don't know. These are
cute, but it's just a little bit too
much like
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know what I want. So, I'm about
to sit here and try to figure it out.
Hopefully, I can figure something out
within the next 20 minutes. Pretty much
all I got, so I'm about to sip my
coffee, scroll down Pinterest, and then
we are going to meet to get my nail
appointment. I don't know what I'm going
to get. Y'all don't know what I'm going
to get. It's just going to be a surprise
at this point, so see you at the nail
appointment, girl.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Y'all, I love my nails.
We generally go stiletto and we go
stiletto French with some polka dots and
a bow. Like, tell me these ain't so cute
and girly. I was going to do pink, but
like I'm just so
>> [gasps]
>> I'm just so like
Girl, something about some stiletto
nails though. Like, let's really get
into it. These are so cute, so cute, so
simple, just how I like them. Just how I
like them. Now, I'm ready to head back
home. I have a few little Sunday things
I need to finish up. I was washing
clothes and
>> [music]
>> There's nobody like your body when you
come [music] on top of me. You're
wearing heaven, baby. You're the closest
thing to heaven me. Oh, but need a
better view. Just show me the real you.
It's always hard.
>> [music]
>> And when I tell you they don't make
music like that no more, they don't make
music like that. They don't. They just
don't. I'm finna put on some lip gloss.
I'm finna hit the house, y'all. I got a
few more Sunday things to do. I might
cook dinner, I might not, I'm not sure.
I was really going to make like soul
food, but I don't like feeling rushed.
Y'all know I got work tomorrow. It's
Sunday. I don't know. We going to see
what we going to get into tonight, so
let me go ahead and get on the road,
head back home.
Nails is done. Hair is done.
I'm going to double stack my lashes
later tonight, and I'm going to be full
effect baddie again. Thank you. Good
morning. Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning. Y'all, it is currently
Wednesday, August 5th. It is days later.
It is days later. I am about to head to
work. I feel like it's something in my
eye. Oh my goodness, it is. I'm about to
head to work, y'all. I came on here. I
was going to start my vlog this morning,
do a little get ready with me for work,
but then I realized I left both of my
tripods in my car, so I wasn't recording
nothing this morning. But y'all, I have
just been so lazy and so like I don't
even know how to explain it. Not in a
funk, cuz like I'm perfectly fine, but I
can't get myself to do anything. Like I
haven't been to the gym in a few days. I
haven't been like
keeping up with like myself. I barely
have any lashes in. They're all falling
out. I'm ripping them out. It's time to
get our pink back. It's time to get our
spark back. Like literally, my hair is
done. My hair is done. My nails are
done. We got all that done, and I'm
still just not feeling it. I don't know
what it is. Like I [snorts] think it's
the weather. It's been raining these
past couple days. I also got an energy
drink, cuz today we're going to lock in.
We're going to lock in. We're going to
go to the gym. We're going to redo my
lashes. We're going to do a self-care
night. We're going to try to get our
pink back. I have not been feeling it
lately, so I'm about to go ahead and
start sipping this energy drink.
Um last night I went to sleep mad early,
because I my sleep has been all over the
place, too. Like it's just been weird
vibes, so we're just going to finish off
this video with just trying to get back
to us. Try to get back to routine. try
to get back to, you know, my regular day
girl cuz I'm just not feeling it. I'm
not feeling it. I don't know what it is,
so we're going to shake it. I'm about to
drink this Celsius. I got strawberry
passion fruit. I don't know if I ever
had this one. Maybe I did a while ago,
but we're going to see. I know I've had
mango dragon fruit. Strawberry?
Not a fan fave, but it'll do. So, I'm
about to drink this, go to work. After
work, we're going to put on a cute
workout set. We're going to go to that
gym, get this body right.
And we're just going to kind of try to
regroup, girl, so get in and yeah. We'll
kind of chit-chat a little bit later,
kind of talk, just do our little girls
thing, you know. So, let me go ahead and
go clock in and make some money for the
day. And then we can get back to
business. All right, y'all. I am
officially back home. As you can see, I
just changed into a workout set. Let's
get into her. Let me show her. When I
tell y'all wearing cute, girly,
colorful, sexy like workout sets, it
just makes me feel so good. It makes me
want to go to the gym. If I don't have a
cute, girly workout set, guess where I'm
not going? The gym. So, this is like a
mandatory thing for me. I invest my
hard-earned money into these cute
workout sets because I don't know,
something about it just gives me like a
confidence boost to go to the gym cuz I
look cute. Let's get into her. Look at
the color, y'all. I just got her. She's
super cute. I like this color. I think
it looks really good on my skin. I was
going to wear a pant set today, but I'm
doing booty and on booty days I get
extra extra hot. So, pants is a no.
Pants is like for the days where I'm
just doing upper body, doing a cute
little one, two, but like on days I be
working, I'm in shorts. So, let me give
y'all the deets on all my workout sets.
Any workout set you've ever seen me in,
I'm going to show you where to find it,
how to find it, X, Y, and Z. You go to
my TikTok. This is how it looks when you
pull my TikTok account up. You click
showcase. Every single workout set I
have posted is on here. So, I do have
some packages. I got some new workout
sets and a sample from TikTok Shop. So,
I'm trying to really branch out, y'all,
like I have been so discouraged and so
out of it, so I really want to get back
into this bag. I'm telling y'all I keep
saying it, but like I'm telling you that
I am. Yeah, and also y'all, let me show
you. 10K on my cooking page. So now I am
monetized. NOW I CAN MAKE A BAG. NOW I
CAN MAKE A BAG SO YOU BEST BELIEVE I'm
definitely motivated. Now I'm about to
get in that cooking bag. I'm going to do
TikTok shop samples. I'm going to do it
all. I'm going to do it all. I'm going
to lock back in. I got that motivation.
So let's get into a haul of the packages
I got um the past couple days. I did
also get another workout set. I just
don't have it. We got a workout set. So
this is a halter top. It's the same kind
of top I got on. It's not from Coral
Kicks though. It's an army green set
which is very different for me. I don't
have any like army green things. And
this is a pant set so it's not shorts.
It's leggings cuz I need some more
legging sets. So I got this and I also
got it in light pink but I wore it the
other day so she's not available for
show cuz she's dirty. And then I got
another set but this is just a plain
black set cuz I have so many colors but
I don't have like neutrals. You know
what I'm saying? I need some like basics
so I can like mix and match if I want.
So this is just shorts. And I feel like
the halter tops for me are really good
cuz my chest. Then the next set I got I
haven't opened yet. It's a sample from
TikTok shop. Y'all really want to get my
TikTok shop bag but I don't really do
samples so like sellers don't really get
approved in my stuff so I need to lock
in. I do need to lock in cuz I really
want to You know what I'm saying? This
is from Wildflower Cases. It is a phone
case.
Period. It says a gift for your phone.
Oh w f.
Packaging is cute. It matches the case.
This case just gave me like Victoria's
Secret vibes. I really like it. This is
my new case so I'm trying to get in my
pink really bad. Like I'm starting to
love again. As you can tell, I kind of
got tired of playing with pink but now
I'm really loving pink again. Like I
might just decorate my apartment pink
again just cuz I'm loving pink again. I
got this phone case from Wildflower.
Shout out to them. Thank you. I got to
make a little video on that and that is
my haul of everything I got these past
couple days and I'm about to go to the
gym. So I'm about to go and fill my
water bottle up, pack my gym bag. We're
about to go to the gym, get a workout
in. I'm going to record. We need to do
it all. So tonight's going to be a busy
night. So let's go ahead, slow it down
and get into this workout first. All
right. Hey, y'all. I'm back. It is
literally the same day. I took my lashes
off. I just got in the shower, washed my
face. It is 9:48 at night, y'all. I am
about ready to go to bed. Um I just
wanted to come up on here and do a
little chit-chat. I'm literally closing
this vlog out. This vlog was a whole
bunch of nothing. I don't know what it
is, but y'all, I am in such a funk.
Like, I don't want to do nothing. I just
I don't know. I just My content I hate
everything I film. I hate everything I
put out these past couple months. I just
It hasn't been hitting. None of this has
been hitting for me. You feel what I'm
saying? Cuz I don't know. I feel like
I'm kind of losing it. Like, I'm losing
my And I don't know, y'all. I don't know
what's going on with me. I don't know
why I feel the way I feel. Like, life is
okay. Like, life is not bad. I'm not
depressed. I'm not X, Y, and Z. But,
it's like I just I don't know. I'm
losing my spark. I'm losing my shine.
I'm just losing it. And I don't know
what it is. Like, I'm just so blessed
nowadays. I'm just I don't want to film.
Every day is the same thing. It's work,
content, work, content, gym, cook,
clean, work, content, gym. It's the same
thing. And it's like, I know there's
going to be like a lot of
recommendations and stuff in the
comments. Like, "Oh, you should try
this. You should go here." That's not
even necessarily what I'm looking for.
Cuz I don't know. Life is repetitive
right now cuz it literally needs to be.
I need to sit my ass down, save my
money, stack my money. I don't need like
ideas on "Oh, you should go here. You
should do this. You should" That's not
even what I'm looking for. This is just
what life is right now. Sometimes with
life you got to sit your ass down. It's
like it's not filmable. It's not
nothing. I just want to be up on here
filming the same videos every other
week. You feel what I'm saying? Like, I
don't know. Life is just so I'm
grateful. I'm blessed. But, this is just
me like venting. Like, I don't know what
it is. This is why I've been so
inconsistent. And like, I'll post one
week and then I won't post for another 2
weeks. I won't post for another 3 weeks.
Cuz like, I don't know, y'all. Like, I
really am feeling myself fall into a
funk. But, it's like I'm okay. Like, you
know, mentally like I'm okay. It's
nothing wrong with me mentally. It's
just like I'm I don't know. I went to
the gym today. I started filming. Then
I'm like, "I don't want to film this."
Like, I'm bored with it already. I don't
want to film this. I had a terrible
workout. Which is life, of course,
you're going to have those bad days. But
it feels like bad day after bad day
after bad day after bad day. Not bad
day, but like just these black days,
like where I'm just like, "I'm not
feeling this." Or like, you know, I'm
having trouble sleeping and X, Y, and Z.
I'm having trouble just doing the things
I should be doing. Like I'm really
losing it, it feels like. Like I'm
losing my motivation, I'm losing my
inspiration, I'm losing my spark, I'm
losing my shine. Like I feel like my
skin don't even glow the same no more.
If you know anything about me, this skin
be glowing. I feel like it's not. And I
don't know. Like I really have a hard
time putting my emotions into words. I
feel like the girls that get it get it.
But like to a lot of people they're
going to be like, "What the hell are you
talking about? Like what are you even
saying? You're saying a whole bunch of
nothing." Which it definitely comes off
that way, but it's like I can't explain
how I'm feeling. I just know I'm feeling
black. If y'all have any inspiration or
anything to get my spark back, to get my
shine back, to get back doing [\h__\h] Cuz
like I keep trying to force it, but like
forcing it and then also trying to do
content. Like I'm forcing it. Like, you
know, I'm forcing it going to the gym.
Today I went to the gym. Did I really do
anything for real for real?
I I played around that gym. I'm not
going to lie. I did play in the gym.
Like I'm literally forcing this right
now. At least in this vlog I got my hair
done, I got my nails done. It's still
worth a little something. I don't know
how long it's going to be. I don't know
what You know. I know it's not my best
one yet. Yeah, I don't know. Maybe I
just need like a reset, a hard reset,
like not even film type of reset. Like
just really reset and tap back into me
and get back to me and figure out what
Kaya wants in this era, figure out what
Kaya needs, and just pour back into me
for a couple weeks because something is
off, sisters. Something is off and I
couldn't tell you what it is. So, yeah,
that's really just my life. I'm going to
just wrap this video up cuz I feel like
I'm really just forcing it and like
doing a bunch of nothing. So, I'm really
just not even trying to film this no
more. Like when I start a new video I
want it to just be fresh. Like fresh,
something new, something I actually want
to film when I'm feeling myself again.
So, yeah, girly pops, this is all I got
for you. I'm sorry, but I did just want
to show my face and kind of let y'all
know where I'm at mentally, what's going
on, why I'm like so inconsistent yet
again. Don't know when the next video
is, so don't ask. It probably won't be
on another Sunday. Let's just scratch
the posting schedule until we can get
back to feeling like Ky. So, if I say
anything about a posting schedule and
you really holding me to that, just
don't hold me to it no more. Just don't
hold hold it to me. Just don't let it
Just forget it. Forget I even said that.
We'll be back. I really don't want to
keep posting BS and stuff I don't like
until I'm feeling like, "Okay, yeah,
she's back." I just I feel like I'm
half-assing it and I know people are
going to be like, "You know, we want to
see anything you post. You could be
doing this and we'll love it." It's not
even about that. This is a me thing.
Like, as a creator, if you're a creator,
you know yourself. Yes, people would
really watch like some BS you post. But,
as a creator, that's holding myself to
such a low standard. Like, I'M REALLY
THAT'S JUST NOT YOU KNOW, LIKE, I DON'T
KNOW. I feel y'all, but like, me and the
way my head work, it's not going to
work. Love y'all. Hugs and kisses. I
appreciate all the love and support, the
ongoing love and support with no matter
how many breaks I take. I appreciate
everybody who's still here to this day,
who's still watching, who's still
liking, who's still commenting, who's
still a silent viewer. I appreciate you
all. I love you all. But, I'm going to
go ahead and call it a night. Going to
pray on it. And I'll see y'all in the
next video.
Whenever that is.